gr8musik.com 2019-06-17

# gr8musik.com - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY

Your privacy is important to plytxt. So we've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with plytxt or a plytxt affiliated company. plytxt and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

Here are some examples of the types of personal information plytxt may collect and how we may use it.

### What personal information we collect

When you create an plytxt account, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information.

### How we use your personal information

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on plytxt's latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. It also helps us to improve our services, content, and advertising. We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with plytxt, you may not opt out of receiving these communications
